once that wins the tape
the scope is like to be held like this
anyway okay undo the lock oh yeah it's a
little tricky on the iPhone X
warning scobie's well now it's 2 p.m.
are we gonna talk about alright guys so
check out my visitor badge yeah they let
me speak it at home entry school I spoke
to a class of 2nd and 3rd graders I
spoke to a class of 4th and 5th graders
the 2nd and 3rd graders Elon would have
been proud of me
I told him that they should study
physics they were studying Newton's
three laws we do a free body diagram of
a car
we talked about the forces acting upon
the car they got most of them friction
and resistance gravity the normal force
the gas the brakes
I told those kids to study physics now
it's the older kiss and I'm really
talking about how the youth your Walkman
I told the fourth and fifth graders that
they were computers and to think of
themselves as computers they're fine
with it they were fun they looked
worried
yeah they looked they looked very
worried yeah but I think the kids are so
I'm just saying guys the kids are gonna
be okay so that is the good news
let me tell you all the bad news
sorry how many scobie's about 50 welcome
garage door guys there so I'm gonna tell
you guys the bad news the self driving
awareness tour was a dismal financial
failure
how many owns the resale zero one one
bogey someone owe me so one who's old
one what did we actually yeah the self
driving awareness tour was a dismal
financial failure except our beacon
Bitcoin cache was the most profitable
and the guys now talking about how
his donation that amount was a mistake
that he wants 90% back we're of course
honorable people and we're gonna send
him his money back so trying to figure
out I'm still trying to use blocking
work right big good cash guys we were
honestly paid to shell for Bitcoin cash
because we weren't even played we were
just like your deceptive give me a
suggestion and all shelf
yeah we'll show it we were not we were
not it hey no I like guys we were paid
to show we'd be rich right now my desert
the speed up
ya know the self-driving car awareness
to it was a dismal financial failure and
now we have the next thing to talk about
and this is a very serious thing come AI
just like Wikipedia doesn't run for free
so um
I don't know how much longer we're all
going to be around
like I can't bring myself to take more
VC money I just can't do it I can't do
it they're scammers they can't prove it
like I'll let them sink in their claws
with a series a and then before I know
it I'm hiring a corporate communications
department right and corporate
communications departments are one step
towards becoming the companies that I
despise and viv what you got a good
quote before the best way to not get to
a destination begin the journey what
would begin it's even better to better
than I was gonna say start yeah so
everybody oh look Luke 9 Chu said I'd
pay to watch these live streams honestly
please live James that's of course free
but please go to shop comma dot ai and
buy things come one advice words they're
saying they want sure tell your friends
to buy things all the swag is going
massively up in price I'm learning for
my friends at Yvonne change I'm buying
one of those G Vontae hoodies one of
those $13 like Gmail and che-hoo DS when
I get to New York because honestly do
you want to know how he really made
money on this tour we Honnold Bitcoin
which is kind of terrible coming right
now you know how I talked about
profitability that is projection we are
right now not profitable hats would be
great the scope is I say q4 of 2018 2017
has not been a profitable quarter let's
start the auction for beanies okay when
you look at Elon selling hats right Eli
baby made two hundred fifty thousand
dollars off those hats do you understand
that's also the reservation price for
one Tesla Roadster like all the work put
into hats or a single Tesla Roadster $30
beanies as the consensus we could do $30
beanies but guys we're never gonna grow
into a profitable company by selling
beanies we have to sell Aeons pandas and
giraffes a JLS of something says if you
made it more consumer-friendly you'd
blow up overnight talk about that time
kid instead that gets into court for
communications yeah see and that's worse
guys you know what they say I would
rather die with dignity and honor than
sell out
I will die on the ill of dignity and on
I'm just I'm just putting that out there
you know what I mean I'm big on not
selling out these are old-school Punk
values here right like old-school Punk
before Punk sold out that's the real
problem but the youth are woke the youth
are great guys I've had a lot of people
ask me like why why are they called
pandas and like George asked the kid in
every George ass the second and
third-graders every single kid said
because it's black and white yeah like
society makes you and like we asked we
held up a neon and George was like what
what is this and they're like it's above
everyone and everyone else is like you
guys made custom oh no they're really oh
my god okay I'm not gonna say his name
but this is the guy who runs something
that's in our space right who was in our
car in competing and like I let him hold
the EON and I was telling him about how
we have an external GPU in there I just
let him go with his like you guys have
an external GPU and they are like you
know not not like not though what do you
mean
well you tell us who it was after no no
it's not appropriate to call me like
that but I'm like holy you're
literally holding the finger the kids
with the off no it's a phone in a case
they remind me if anyone out there
seemed like the little prince where he
talks about he draws this picture and
every adult thinks it's it's a hat it's
like yeah it looks like it looks like a
hat but in reality it's a snake that's
eaten an elephant and only a child only
the mind of a child could consume such a
thing they just think no no you know I'm
12 forever you know we're like Metro
alright I'm Fanning a bud I just saw
repeat command like metros lock she was
a seventeen forever seventeen forever
you know here's no that songs about
statutory rape
team forever we yeah
with this
yeah
to mention station bras
yeah we are we on the radio right now we
did a lot of Sioux Falls radio you guys
know how the TV in Kansas City went I
think I terrified the floor recorder
yeah we should know like wait yes never
know you know I like my wife said I just
couldn't say no Chris you are helping me
Chris your videos help already the wheel
yeah it's windy right now it's windy so
okay we have a there's an angle offset
learner in the in the code and with the
wind changes the angle offset learner
has to relearn and this thing's got like
a slow low-pass filter so it takes a
little bit of time to relearn the wind
once we have good localization shipped
see things like pigeons we have good
localization that we'll be able to
adjust for the wave in a couple seconds
like how a person does but right now
it's getting confused by the wind
someone was asking when to open pilot
4.0 it's actually 0.4 0.4 when that's
coming out and the release is going to
happen hey if anyone from comas watching
I think we're ready yeah we're ready
look at this nice shade of orange guys
it shows the it shows the parts uploaded
we've heightened emerging in RDX support
Acura RDX I went out there got our stuff
working for the RDX so I'm not sure
exactly what the status of that is but
congratulations it's close enough to the
other stuff I think we can probably work
it into virtually Chris said I need to
make a new video ASAP because I think
people keep building Neos but they got a
Mikey on put a link to you in one of
your videos to be honest I will announce
this beyond sales have outstripped the
number of Neos we've seen turned on so
we are selling yawns we're just aren't
selling but not be on set to sustain
comment I'm actually not that far off
these Shopify stories do it so much
better than this to the Shopify store
sells more in a day that we sold on this
whole tool
yeah
pretty Pam's to resale total sellout
yeah yeah our last guys I'm Rahul peep
does it coeliac to her it's not
profitable
every little peep stores bomb well
that's you know what it is no
sells tickets yeah honestly I better
three mobile t-shirt sales
no charge
Gregory's asking where we headed next I
think it's right on the border they beat
him like walk to both sides most of its
in Wisconsin
yeah yeah so that's her stop and I plan
on going at open mic night their boss
George is gonna do some slam poetry
check it out SoundCloud are cops like
Tom Cruise
Helly boys asking will you carry on
supporting vo - we're not gonna do
anything to intentionally break it but
we're not really going to test on it
yeah no one paid anything for Neos from
us so we don't really feel about doing
that it's kind of like ripping pandas on
the original board they still work but
expect to have to do a bit of
maintaining yourself a lot more than me
okay we just don't have the manpower
it's honestly it's manpower guys it's
not even like a planned obsolescence
thing it's like no it's it lowers our
release checklist yeah yeah Lube 9 she
was asking about someone who has a
kind of store installing these for
people and selling them hey we're big
fans we can definitely do volume
discounts we've already sold to Panthers
with volume discounts give our discount
to be honest so yeah if someone's
looking to set that kind of stuff up
but yeah guys I'm like Jimmy Wales here
you know Jimmy Wales is it's not gonna
be able to afford 5-star dinners in
first-class tickets anymore because you
know we were talking about last night we
were like how can we cut back on beef
really I don't I don't get a salary but
seriously guys I do want to count yeah
that's very sweet
we're gonna we're gonna cancel my health
insurance scam anyway if Obamacare
allows it oh I thought we had freedom in
this country said he tried that tried
why yeah virtually chris says he puts a
note on everyone's car with Honda
sensing I had to pay one year the
Obamacare fine I'm so bad if I found out
about this
this isn't joke like I thought we had
freedom I'm all for universal healthcare
this is someone's I see about
bulk ordering you can email support if
you talk about email bull
Shannon come AI goes to Devon all to be
honest no respect your view no
coming I all read it I still won't reply
but right away like this you know it's
we have filters for certain words I'm
not gonna say what words because then
people might not put them but they just
go right into the I guarantee you guys
know what the best partnership is right
purchase order I'll pull request you're
grateful partnerships too they all start
with P two of them a real
I'm banning all these people that are
feeding just blocking a band number one
yeah
hey somebody traffic yeah yeah thank you
gundarr day that's more traffic so long
trip do so dress so one drive okay we're
now tied from this let's see guys we're
up to one draft let's see how many sales
we can get on chopped combo AI right now
we're showing for us we're not showing
up in cash more than often is asking how
many employees does coming to many many
all UPS guys layoffs if you're out
watching it come nai there won't really
be layoffs don't worry
you just have to rent out parts of the
office yeah we're gonna Airbnb do we
maybe the office but yeah guys but
someone's asking about the PID feedback
loop again if we're not but we using a
PID feedback we barely at all it's
almost all feed-forward a lot of us
switched over to have to see now
it's still a little bit of the Idina
still MSNBC which actually addicted it
was never even a PID loop who was a P I
loop don't be d right guys no the Crips
they don't like words words with sees it
sounds like not an B's it sounds like we
could actually make a lot of money
renting out a room in the house to see
how we operate people say they love to
stay in the hall already oh yeah know
what I really want to do is build some
of those you guys see like the homeless
people in San Francisco started to have
like tiny houses on the street right I
want to build a few of them in Airbnb
them yeah because like a hipster
experience yeah thank God they give you
tough Network wow really
more comments a lot of them came all at
once I couldn't really read them
you guys should do an eon giveaway to
enter you must buy a hoodie going off
January 1st every with pandas used to be
$88 those are the good old days the
opposite of the hardware startup that
like price is insanely high and then
lowers the price reasonably then they
get less reasonable like rest in peace
Fantine rested be snappy oh yeah I know
but if you don't want family I'd end up
like NAFTA shop code I buy stuff tell
your friends because you know it's our
life out here
there's there's a there's a wired
article this morning talking about how
startup founders are not the good guys
we're the bad guys Sean's asking did a
major investor pull out this sounds like
you guys are panicking well that we
really are broke we're certainly not
even you know why no investor pulled out
because we didn't have any investors
pull it I really hate most investors
like like like the way they talked and
the language they use it was like I
don't want to be a part of this scam
yeah no no no a lot of people email us
to invest but you see that's the thing
about investment right you want to sell
what you produce you don't want to sell
your soul I don't understand company to
celebrate after they raise an investment
around what you've done was literally
just sell part of your soul
yeah so I was asking are we our most
profitable almost yeah we're almost
brothers you know we were hoping we'd be
profitable on this tour but we've
learned that we are almost profitable as
we want to do it that way
sweet we are looking at a profitable q1
of next year for yeah I mean that's how
we got to do it that's how we got to do
we have not had a profitable quarter
yeah Pete the system we've definitely
had profitable weeks probably in
profitable months but our first
profitable corridor will really be
that's a real company yeah vanilla
gorillas joining the scope we're talking
about how the self-driving awareness to
her was not a profitable endeavor no
there was a huge supporter of us we
definitely thank you and thank you
make sure to track your panda sales from
Sioux Falls and next 24 hours we will do
that Isaac via the website yeah we'll
see if we get more orders from the place
actually uh to be honest guys if you
place orders right now we'll ship them
out tomorrow on the road we're gonna be
like ham girls or gamers the way we
shout out the people alone this is the
telethon periscope yeah you woke up no
bubble seriously we're shipping out
tomorrow we have like what do you got we
got nine yawns in the car yep if you get
in right now
yeah we got like 30 pandas probably more
than half of those are sold but like
Jamaican jewels asking when our pigeon
for the orders coming out follow pigeons
well we're gonna give away the first
pigeons we can even lay the first
pigeons to people who are top young
users probably second week of January if
you were a top young user I don't care
if Dilton pilot or ship applause if
you're a top of yon user may be the top
five wil get free pigeons right we
always give us a like Rev B pandas break
themselves I'm grandpa pandas have like
a serious hardware bug and after you
flash them a bunch of times they break
themselves but the nice thing is nobody
paid a dollar for every badness so we
got to but we got to sell commented but
well coma didn't restore money right so
that's kind of our like our alpha
hardware program right yeah I'm the a
barber program we don't we don't to
charge money for bad heartburn right
yeah we definitely want to stand behind
what we sell so we give a few away first
make sure they're good pigeons will work
great with your existing zoo pigeons
connector they've been over the ideas
they do work with the yawns yeah well
shop.com though I buy things take off
this sticker the next person to buy
something maybe after I'll take the
fleece off
all right - fun
hoppin do you guys pay yourselves out
salaries are literally lit not everyone
gets a salary with me guys I live in the
office we didn't know you guys you guys
know when I will start taking salary
though a big salary much for profitable
no and seriously - every CEO out there
if you have an unprofitable company you
should really feel shame taking a salary
it's disgusting people who like oh yeah
now we lost the company thirty million
dollars but uh I get a two million
dollar bonus why bro
why you literally had one job as CEO
um but ya know once once you're
profitable reinvest most of it everybody
gets raises I get a salary now that's
still that's still aways away we have a
lot of reinvestment
lot of reinvestment a lot of growth
probably looking at a salary list 2018
five the good news is you have a Bitcoin
and uh no matter
now loop nine to put a red comma dot a I
box logo on your hoodies and sell them
for $300 they're going up
oh honey hoodies our hoodies are going
up to 250 cuts yeah you used to get two
hoodies for 129
now you only get one but these are about
to go up to 250 Cooper no once you get
to have it's like the the thing like the
dream
what is your plan to win the Adhan
oh I'd always tell the youth about them
yeah that was a good old to you yeah I
told you every self-driving car company
out there is learning from a fleet of
vehicles right there's no other real way
to do this but every time weibo wants to
add a vehicle to their fleet we'll have
to go and buy a car so it's maybe Cory's
your cheap cars are only thirty thousand
dollars for 30 to 40 but do they have to
spend like two hundred thousand dollars
on sensors they got a lot of expensive
lidar sensors and computers they
probably got to spend another hundred
thousand now probably probably more like
twenty thousand on the retrofit so we're
gonna get $250,000 for the way no car
alone and then they have to pay a driver
so adding a car to the weibo fleet costs
way mo a lot of money ahead of your car
to the kama fleet actually makes kama
money and that's the distinction and
that's how we're gonna win
right they're paying for something that
we are getting paid right this is a lot
like going to college kids don't go to
college you want an education go to go
get a job at Google you'll learn more
and they pay you
vanilla Grill is asking if they can come
build pigeons with baby yeah
first one why don't you guys be selling
hardware with open-plan
harder with the open pilots
yes maybe a year maybe a year you think
about it so when we do sell hardware
with open pilot time so right now we
only sell dash cams fairly unregulated
and when we do sell hardware that is
designed to drive a car we will have to
register as a as probably I'm not a
hundred percent sure on this but the way
it's looking now is what our register is
a vehicle manufacturer with nishta so
there's a bit of legal overhead there
and then there's a bit of a liability
risk where you know right now you
downloaded software from github so
justjust just remember that reliability
is it's great and so it allows things
like open pilot to be possible for us to
for us to give it away like this before
we before we actually sell things with a
pilot we need a few things we need money
for the legal overhead we need to make
sure our reporting stuff is very very
reliable right it was a man in
Pennsylvania who swerved across four
lanes of traffic in his Tesla caused an
accident and then when he was stopped by
the police and they're like why did you
do that he's like a well auto pilot did
it and this is what he was reporting to
the media and then of course Tesla
ducked into the loft on his logs of his
cars
he had never turned on autopilot so we
have to make sure we can prevent
scenarios like that with good logging
and we also have to make sure we
understand what the classes of
disengagement SAR and report that to
users much better we have to make it
like very clear in the user manual look
here's a scenario where your car could
mess up we have to know kind of what
roads people should expect it works on
we got a we got to work up to that yeah
so I think I think probably by the end
of next year we can sell even this
hardware with with open pilot but for
now we only sell dashcam and the reason
you can modify of is because what kind
of a hypocrite would I be this is like a
line I give now if I didn't let you
modify your products however you that
you paid for where can you pay for them
I'd shopped on Ramadani I go buy buy buy
have you had offers from major
automakers to get bought now yes so
here's my here's my thought on getting
water I would be fine with being
acquired by a company who wants to
continue our mission if some company if
I believe that getting bought by a
company would further what we are trying
to do here at common AI I would
seriously consider the offer the truth
is if you get bought by a major
automaker you're gonna sit around for
years before you ship anything like
groups
automakers aren't gonna let us depart
not not gonna let a cruise do but see
cruise doesn't really shift anything
yeah right I think that there's gonna be
around I don't know that much now I knew
a lot about at the beginning of the TM
cruise relationship alright we'll see
we'll see how long before it's actually
in consumers hands I mean you see how
extremely conservative wavers be
extremely concerned you know way mo
should do they should bring on Travis
collecting the CEO I would actually be
afraid of way mo with Travis's CEO
possible so anti go well but hey man it
would be a great move right look look at
Hoover falling apart right over just got
regulated the EU is a taxi service
you think Travis will let that happen no
way Travis we're here we're trying to
help you out I would love to see you
make a jobs you can return to the hollow
over and if you're interested they
become nai if you're looking for a job
if you're looking to buy things that
shop.com and Dante I we sell everything
you see here is for sale all of this
hardware and this software it's not even
for sale it is completely free at github
calm such coming so much open pilot
actually not this version this version
hasn't been released yet but it will be
released today or tomorrow by the time
your eon arrives if you so choose to
modify it to install this software
top that commonality the orders come in
anyone checking few orders coming in
heavy check so check the orders are
coming in yeah I'm done with the sticker
man but I know I have high hopes for the
future guys hey you kids never sell out
I don't understand how the same kids who
listen to like you know amplify Good
Charlotte grew up to be some of the
scumbags I meet in society today but ya
know that's a problem the automaker's we
also got approached by automakers who
want to work with right automakers who
want to maybe put our technology in
their cars right and we first started
come hey I thought that this actually
might be a possibility so we've been
entertain meetings remember when we made
with the auto makers oh yeah we used to
have these people in right they loved
them walk into her I know I'm like not
know what I will I will call them out at
this one I will call out Jaguar Land
Rover and buy like I don't really
remember what the meeting was but we're
leaving they asked if we could call him
a taxi call like an ogre or a left it's
just like I would never take it over
it's not licensed stop no Susan you that
story
oh and I'm like okay this is hopeless
right I just took you for a ride in a
new a self-driving car with a computer
in the back
see like this even before it looked less
polished than this but I'm like this is
hopeless right it's not even like you
know it's it's passed by some police on
market my ways mark of my ways first to
make sure we're not getting pulled over
yeah I think we're not getting pulled
over every time I see a police and I
like watch him in my rearview mirror and
I watch him go away you get that feeling
in your alright you get that like wolf
feeling in your arm like I don't think I
was speeding so open pilot was driving
my speed is set to five miles over the
limit it's probably going a little
slower cuz the car in front of me in
honor of the police we're gonna pretty
visit
1,006 up 23 all right guys these orders
eight oh yeah you can make this go up we
made please buy our things selling our
things is the only thing that makes us
profitable it's the only thing that
funds great things like the self driving
awareness tour because someone's got a
spread awareness and awareness ain't
free so what's asking about pilot slows
down for emergency vehicles like when
there are sirens no no we're not at that
level yet the the open file will slow
down your vehicle when the car but you
know it is a level two system you are
still in control vehicle at all times
yep if you alone oh no my to balance
alright should we do the Toyota gallon
challenge where we just keep going let's
just keep going guys guys arm up
just I'm ready to die today
just kidding I'm ready to run out of gas
though yeah no but honestly I don't know
man how long before okay so the course
says we have sixty miles
at least 20 days so we actually have
like 50 miles left Toyota you know I
don't know why we didn't realize you
know what I was saying yesterday about
the news like if you know something
about like you know the news right says
you're a farmer right and you know a lot
about farming and you watch with the
news says about farming you're like wow
this is all total total crap right and
then you watch the news report about AI
and you're like it's really interesting
the way they're making a person of an AI
a person in Saudi Arabia hey you don't
have that same critical eye to realize
that's all right I don't know
why that like humans aren't good at
thinking about this but like we fell
into the same fallacy I really did
the speedometer on the car says that we
are going 74 miles we're actually going
70 so if this is pedometer lies to you
why would we not think the gas gauge
yeah but we knew it lied to us we just
did nobody how much we should have
guessed that it was an outrageous amount
we'll stop for gas chill for a little
bit then we get back on the scope and
we'll call it by things shop comma dot
AI this bridge is brought to you by your
charge of reminding if you guess the
correct one that we sponsored the
product with the British sponsored by
you get to buy two so once that those
hidden gallons are used to cool the fuel
pump you could burn the fuel pump by
running too low over the MT wait how do
you use that to cool the
doesn't let seeking ways like displays
work to the point that I could like ask
it to like take me to a gas station
I'm not really good at using what you
have a certain number of ways
oh we gotta have ways you and as bad as
you all submerge like this but you
should share course
Oh gas
see if you're allowed to what see if
it's also smart enough to realize that I
don't want to go five miles of that one
I had two RVs apple turnovers which
sound like a great idea at the time but
yeah ways this week oh there's still
hard Oh fast it was like what if they're
actually not lying to us like guys we
have 12 bottles actually Chris was
saying he can't come to Philly anyways
so you're done with the tour folks this
is it this is this is so a snow peas are
calling you out that you missed an
overpass oh my god you're right that
overpass is brought to you by the comedy
[Music]
yeah tell about what we learned about
with what thought more we learned and
then tell them about the challenge you
tell me so we're you know we're looking
up at windmills how much power they
generate so much these windmills are
rated for about two to three megawatt
and I was like now we're waiting there's
like no way yeah so it's more like it's
more like a few hundred kilowatt I don't
know I think that's Chandler's generated
on a normal day I think in a whole year
we generate about 8,000 to 10,000
megawatts amortized over at yeah over
the whole year play gate gigawatts knows
800 and see if those bastards for the
world this is a challenge man humanity
manatee okay and so we looked up how
much power humanity was using I think it
wasn't even a terawatt there wasn't no
yeah we're doing at it you know it was
it was it was like disappointingly small
yeah maybe it was just America there was
only using like like I didn't use more
than America but we can use more than
America versus it was like 500 gigawatts
was pathetic um so I think conservation
is one of the dumbest ideas ever
invented
you want conservation go back and live
in the Stone Age right efficiency is
great electric cars great things like
this that can use energy more
efficiently are great but we should also
be using more energy so I'm challenging
right here on this periscope humanity to
the 10 terawatts challenge
by the year 2025 humanity should be
using 10 terawatts empower you somebody
here watch over your unit of its watt is
a Joule per second man so we should be
using 10 terror joules of energy per
second on average I think that yeah what
average obviously kind of like like the
humanity uses different amounts of
energy at different times right home
depending on which countries in the
light which countries in the dark but
yeah I think that that ok 7 miles to
work I think that humanity can do it
10 terawatts challenge Oh guys no really
like let me tell you why conservation is
done right like a lot of people you know
they're like oh I'm a conservationist
and I'm all for things like conserving
you know conserve the rainforest
conserve you know biodiversity of these
things are great when it comes to
conserving power it's like we can just
make more power and making more power is
actually one of the greatest things you
can do to increase people's standards of
living
all right standard of living is highly
correlated to how much power you're use
we've given you a little bit of a heads
up or if we can use more power as a
species we can raise everyone's standard
of living
conservation stupid efficiency great
more power great the service is brought
to you by the car my type and at $99 by
December 31st or $200 by afterward after
generators but this is a coming i panda
they're for sale on our store for $99
right here you can see that the panda
that's actually driving us right now is
here this is just the exact same panda
that you can buy for only $99 it's a
universal car interface and connects
this port on your car to your USB port
and your Wi-Fi of your computers it's a
bridge from cars to computers and they
are available for the amazingly low
price of only $99 right now at chop
comedy I so if everybody you could go
there and buy a panda and if you buy in
the next 10 minutes I'm pretty sure that
you're gonna get your panda shipped out
tomorrow if you buy a week from now
we're all going home for the holidays
but if you buy right right now I think
we really only have like ten of these
left
no we're playing the other ones already
committed I'm sure we got enough orders
to ship out the rest
oh yeah all our orders that come in AI
or a pipe up so they really are we are
probably about 10 of these left
available this year if you want them to
ship out to Mars you can buy this at
shop kamidana hi that's shop which I
don't know how to spell dot comm a dot a
I like artificial intelligence next item
you can buy is brought to you by this
bridge which is the giraffe for a low
low cost of $60 for $60 you can get
yourself a giraffe see that this travel
ready has a panda attached to wrap you
could just unplug this panda right like
this separate this is a Toyota giraffe
this is a Honda giraffe we of course
have these available right here in the
Cobb a Bulbul store but since we do not
have any more stops on this tour we're
gonna ship out all the items in the
mobile store to use scope he's at home
go to shop comm got a I buy it right now
only $60 search like Chris was asking
about updating a panda with a neon with
the restart of the phone that is correct
your flasher panda if necessary started
its me to why the animal names we
explained earlier how and us our pandas
straight forward this black is why you
find one like a pet it's like a panda
and the kids were they were they a
yellow right away you know just don't
like society make you overthink things
that's right as an anthem don't let
society make you feel guilt guilt is the
worst emotion ever and none of the
overpasses are brought to you by guilt
because you shouldn't feel guilty about
anything you should wake up and you
should feel unless you did something
terrible just wake up and they feel
guilty about like eating the last cookie
throw yourselves
yeah we will create your problems and
then sell you things to remove we didn't
create any of your problems we just sell
things to make your life better
yeah the day that I'm creating your
problems I'm a miserable guy and I will
never do that long as I'm CEO of comedy
I'm this way I can't work in security
Security's a huge stamp it's fear
mongering mongering about something you
should worry about it your life that's
very different
fear mongering would be like if we
talked about the car crashes never go we
talk about how it makes your life better
improving the baseline like yeah but
capitalism as flaws was lot better than
we've tried before and the real problem
capitalism is rent-seeking as long as
you can avoid rent-seeking
capitalism is great capitalism you're
the whole basis of capitalism is consent
its consent between a buyer and a seller
right there would be no sale if both the
buyer and the seller don't agree on the
crimes we can obviously say please go to
shop Khamenei I admire things but if you
go there and you're not willing to pay
that price look we're willing to sell it
for that price you can decide yourself
whether you're going to buy it for that
price and that's why capitalism
about consent unlike some other isms
which are about you make told what to do
town she give you freedom this is
America and we love free
got to be official super8 we're talkin
saucy and didn't I
was coming at your first job at the co
no is my second marketing I worked at a
marketing PR firm thanks yeah it's my
second as well
lucky Bartley major defense corporation
we try to not hire people right out of
college we'll hire people either right
out of high school or out of their first
job because college brainwashes you for
four years yeah college is a really bad
deal guys we got 16 I guess someone's in
Minneapolis and said they'll come meet
us in the cross yeah Gregory Marouf Oh
Sadie's very cool this way if you guys
see any gas yeah
so who wants us to open a comical George
I was going telling you if I'm 50 and
there's still little celerity yeah where
is it
I don't know what I could do to do
anything
[Music]
I think autopilot is a general store
never see movies have never seen it no
I'm sure they have I just thought for
the first time we're not come on any
scope he's don't lie to me or go to 90
that way we can experience some of all
right welcome to stop in for gas with us
this is the first place we're kind of
bringing you to yeah um you guys can
want to come in is that guy squealing
screams whoa gasps I like the choices
only two
no choices bad y'all see although
chairman checkout 75 uploads remaining
that's that's the new thing yeah how
many parts we've uploaded I think that
the way this is like Parador internal
account that's not really gonna work
your experience will be much better than
ours new destination will take you in
two ways oh yeah we're really gonna
start with like I think maybe we do
leave the scope bees out but they just
the best of us whatever well you know
what they say about a good thing you got
to let it go and if it comes back to you
okay alright we'll see oh no scope is by
thinks shot back home and are they I
will see you soon